It's amazing... You'd never
even think we were on a ship.
This is the renowned official
casino ship of Port Verlington.
Apart from the casino,
there are restaurants, a pool bar,
and a beauty spa as well as
anything else you can imagine.
Are those people all gamblers?
No no... Most of them are just
moderately rich with free time,
and looking to have a night
of dreams and excitement.
By the way, where is Dante?
He doesn't seem to be around...
This way.
Two pairs.
My apologies, but I believe
this hand is mine.
Three of a kind.
Dammit...
Well, no big deal... This
game's just getting underway.
The fun's just beginning.
Yes. I'm looking forward to it.
The longer one gambles, the
more interesting it becomes...
The same as a kiss.
If you can beat me,
I'll give you a long kiss, the likes of
which you've never experienced before.
That's something to look forward to.
I'd better be careful not to
lose the clothes off my back here!
The man who just won is Gold-Arm
Joe, said to have a "Golden Arm."
The woman across the table is also famous.
It's said that she has the luck of a
goddess. She's known as "Lucky Amanda."
The elderly man next to her is "Santa Claus,"
a poker ace that they say
can read people's thoughts.
All these people are trying to act so refined,
but their eyes are burning with greed.
Well, are we ready for another game?
Please... Save my husband, Paul.
He likes to gamble?
Yes, he was a straight-and-narrow
man before we got married...
But it's like he became a different person
all of a sudden, and got addicted to gambling.
Gambling is like a sickness.
But there's one big difference.
There is no medicine you
can take to cure yourself of it.
You might as well just give up on him.
Please! If my husband goes
on like this, he could be killed!
Come on...
Hey, don't be so cold, Dante.
Huh?
You should always be nice to women.
Plus, it may not sound like it,
but this job could be up your alley.
Next one, please.
Pass.
R-Raise. I'll raise you 500.
--Fold.
--I'm dropping out too.
I'll call.
Call.
Three of a kind.
Nothing.
Sorry kids, full house.
If this keeps up, it looks like I'll go
home with a bag full of money again tonight!
I see, so that's why you're
"Santa Claus." It's a clever nickname.
Thank you.
When this game's over, let
me treat you to breakfast.
Sure. That is, as long as you're not
thrown out by then for being flat broke.
We have quite a collection of
inflated egos here, don't we...
By the way, have any of you heard
of a gambler known as "King"?
Yes, one hears about him quite a lot of late.
Apparently he's supposed to be a gambler
from hell who takes the lives of his opponents.
Hmph! Nothing but silly rumors!
They certainly are.
However, it is true that a certain number
of gamblers have died after losing to him.
Who is this King?
Some say he is an aged
man with a white beard.
Others say King is a
beautiful, charming woman.
But the truth is that no one knows for sure.
Yet if such a person actually existed,
wouldn't you love to try a game with them?
King?
Yes. It's said he's a
gambler who brings death.
There have been a number of well-known
gamblers who've recently gone missing.
The only common thread is...
They all went out to play cards,
and then they never came back.
Before long there were rumors
all over the city with people saying
that anyone who plays
this "King" will end up dead.
So, this "King" could be a devil?
If that's true, I guess I
gotta gamble with the devil.
You'd probably be better off not doing that.
I mean, you totally suck at gambling.
Can you recall how much
money you owe me right now?
That's just because I'm nice
to the women when I play.
Hey Dante, when are you gonna pay
out for our game you lost to me earlier?
I'm nice to the women and children.
But how do I find a guy when I
don't even know what he looks like?
If I just randomly play cards looking for
him, it could take an infinite amount of time.
--And infinite money.
--Shut up.
A letter?
It's an invitation to that luxury cruise ship
turned casino operating in the next town over.
It was sent by "King."
Since he went to the trouble to invite
us, it would be bad form not to accept.
And since you'll be going anyhow,
you can grant that woman's request.
You did say you're nice to
women and children, didn't you?
Damn.
I don't know who this "King" guy is,
but he seems like a stuck-up snob.
But it's interesting.
If "King" is really here
among us, and I beat him,
my reputation will soar even higher.
Yeah, if King is among us,
you'll eventually find out.
3,000.
Fold. I'm out.
I fold, too.
I don't have enough chips.
Well then, I guess you'll just
have to sit there and watch quietly.
I'll raise...
I'll raise 5,000.
Ohhh! The game is on!
Hey, you.
You're shaking.
Don't you think you'd better go home,
before you make your pretty wife cry?
Leave me alone! Just be quiet!
Well, let's see 'em.
He's holding three of a kind...
his face down card
could give him a full house...
Just to be safe...
All ready. I'm in for everything.
Well, it's time for a showdown then.
Full house!
F-Four of a kind!
I... I did it... I won! I won!
I won!
Th-That's not...
Sir?
He's dead...
Could this possibly mean that you are "King"?
N-No!
What are you saying?
I... I'm...
Just take it easy... Let's take a breather.
Miss, call the person in charge.
And I'd like a hot cappuccino, too.
Right away, sir.
Wherever King appears, that
place is governed by Death's rules.
Maybe the rumors are true.
I wonder...
If you're scared, you should just head
home, get in bed, and go to sleep.
Well, aren't we arrogant...
Maybe you're King?
Well, we'll know the truth soon enough.
This is going to be a lot of fun.
You can have your fun, but don't you think
you're the most likely to go broke next?
The real pleasure of gambling
is turning the tables completely
in the final moments of the game.
What are you talking about?!
You're losing just like
we predicted, aren't you?
You're totally hopeless without me.
I'll take over from here.
Hey, Patty!
Interesting...
It's best to teach them just how cruel
the world can be while they're still young.
You're...
I didn't expect to see you here.
I heard there was a big poker tournament
on this ship, and I just had to come.
Are you that worried? I'm jealous.
It's okay. Your husband hasn't lost anything.
As of yet, at least...
You're not going to go see him?
No. It's not like I could
get him to stop anyway.
I see.
What? This child is really playing for him?
This isn't a kid's game.
I'm not here for kids' games!
So you can lose the pompous
attitude until you beat me.
Deal the cards!
What the hell... what's Patty doing here?
Well now that she's here,
there's nothing we can do about it.
Damn...
Well? Did you figure out who this "King" is?
Not yet. He's a clever one.
I guess you just have to keep
winning and stay in it until the end.
Guess so...
It's a risky bet.
But then that's what gambling's
all about, now isn't it?
Be careful.
Sure.
Come on, honey, make up your mind.
Are you in or are you out?
You seem to have aptitude,
but you've got a long way to go.
Time for a substitution.
Why! What the heck?!
I was just getting warmed up!
This is my job.
Man...
Nice work.
I played it safe like you told
me, but these people are good.
Dante's going to get eaten alive...
That I don't doubt at all.
But Dante's got a job to do, and
that's a game he never loses at.
The only thing we can do now is
have a coffee and pray he succeeds.
Fine then. But I'll take tea.
Coffee's too bitter for me.
Okay, okay.
I fold.
Hmmm... Two pairs, eh?
She's the only one who seems
to have a decent hand this time.
With those cards,
she could have three of a kind...
If she does, I'm finished.
Ah, she always plays with
her hair when she's bluffing...
She's not holding three
of a kind. It's a bluff!
I'll call and raise 8,000.
--I fold.
You're smart boys--
I'll call you and raise you 15,000. All in.
Trying to bring me down with a bluff?
I see right through you, young lady.
Fine, it's on. I'm all in.
I call.
Looks like I got you, Grandpa.
Three of a kind.
I win.
So you did get me... Looks
like senility is setting in for me.
Please excuse me.
The loser will silently
take his leave from the stage.
Now we know for sure.
Someone here is "King."
Let's continue the game.
Interesting... But I won't lose
out to anyone with my luck.
You watch, I'll annihilate this "King."
It's just not normal. Don't any of
these people think they can lose?
Aren't they scared of dying?
Straight flush... I win.
That can't be!
I'm known as Lucky Amanda!
How could I lose...
That's another one. Now it's...
Yeah. This is the end game.
Well, I guess it comes
down to you and me then.
I didn't think you'd be
left standing this long...
If I beat you here, that would make me King!
Well, deal the cards!
Here we go.
What's with these hands?
So in the end, each of them could
be holding a royal straight flush?!
That's not...
All in.
You're still on your fourth card.
It looks like both of us have
got a final attack to launch.
How about we say that whatever
happens next, we showdown?
Fine... So it's all or nothing.
I accept. But I'm low on chips.
If I lose, I'll pay the difference
with my life. Sound good?
Done.
Now, let's have that last card!
So, it's a showdown!
A king of hearts! That's
a royal straight flush!
And Dante?!
Royal straight flush.
When two players have the
same hand, spades win.
S-Sara... I'm sorry...
He did it! Dante won, Morrison!
Morrison?
There's nothing in this world
as interesting as gambling...
Especially when people
are betting their lives.
Dante?!
It's the greatest!
Dante, what are you doing?!
This isn't over yet.
Lady, the next game's against you.
The rules are simple.
Whoever gets a bullet through
the other's heart first, wins.
Dante...
Dante!
Stop!
Why?! Why would you shoot him,
Lady?! He's your friend, isn't he?!
Let go of me, Morrison! Let go!
Dante!
Congratulations.
I suppose that you are tonight's winner.
You...
So in the end, you're shot
and killed by your own friend.
Not bad... It makes for
quite a beautiful ending.
Stay back!
So you're the devil... this King?!
You're half right and half wrong.
What do you mean by that?
It didn't matter who played the role of King.
Whoever held an item into which
I bestowed my magical powers
would be captivated by gambling
in exchange for extraordinary luck.
And that person would act as King.
I wish this man had won for me,
but maybe I was hoping for too much.
So it was a trap from the beginning?
Please don't fret!
Soon, you'll be as dead as he is.
As will those two, and all
the passengers on the ship!
Sorry to spoil your party...
But I've been waiting for this moment.
The moment when you showed
your face to brag about your victory.
Dante!
How did you...
You're wondering if your magic failed on me?
No, it worked just fine.
I figured out what was
going on by chance, really...
Patty?
A game, Dante.
Let's play a game...
Are you going to die, or am I?
Patty?!
Stop it!
And that's how I figured it out.
The "mechanism," so to speak, of King.
You were using this to turn regular
people into King and control them.
So you just pretended to
be possessed by its magic?
No, I was entirely possessed by it.
I knew it was the only way to keep winning,
stay in the game and ultimately draw you out.
It was a gamble.
I avoided hitting your
heart as promised, didn't I?
Actually, you grazed it a bit.
Practice your shooting.
Damn...
I've got a lesson for you.
Gambling is something you
do without intermediaries!
My, my, you're a tough one.
You're not going to be able to
harm me with weapons like that.
Okay then... How about this?
Dante!
King of hearts.
Ace of spades.
I win.
So basically, it was all part of your plan.
You letting yourself be possessed,
then having Lady snap you
out of it if push came to shove?
Hey, I said I was sorry already, didn't I?
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Come on, let's do this.
You sure sound confident.
You got some good cards?
Hmmm... I'll pass this time.
I'll take three.
All right... let's see who's got what.
A full house! How do you like that?
Royal straight flush.
I win.
We'll just tack your losses onto your debt.
Damn...
The hell with this.
My father betrayed demonkind,
and fought for mankind.
from the human perspective,
he's a legendary hero.
In the minds of the devils, he's
the culprit of an inexcusable crime.
But... There may have been
some devils out there
who could understand my father's thinking.
If there really is such a devil out there,
I'd sure like to meet him.